

VAN TABBERT

MOBILE AND WEB DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Full stack web and mobile application developer with experience using modern JavaScript libraries and native Android development. Analytical problem solver with the ability to quickly learn new technologies and languages. Skilled multitasker comfortable working within a team and independently. Enthusiastic mentor motivated to guide other developers to their full potential.

CONTACT ME

t: (817) 908-7911

e: van.tabbert@gmail.com

w: www.vannya.me

f facebook.com/vannienicole

github.com/vannya

in linkedIn.com/in/vannya

twitter.com/vannyalock

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Strong: ReactJS, React Native, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, ES6, Redux, React Router V4, Reach Router, Node.js, Express, Sass, Wordpress, Git/Version Control, Photoshop, InDesign.

Knowledgable: Electron, SQL, MongoDB, Webpack, GraphQL, Android, php, Java, C++, Illustrator

CERTIFICATIONS

FCC Front End Certificate Feb 2018
Android Basics Nanodegree Apr 2018
Full Stack Dev Nanodegree May 2018
Front End Dev Nanodegree Jul 2018
React Nanodegree Aug 2018

VOLUNTEER

Mercy House Aug 2014 - Oct 2017 Photographer

Girl Scouts of USA Aug 2010 - May 2012 Daisy and Brownie Leader

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

May 2018 - present

Walmart - Bentonville, AR

- Develop internal applications using both React and React Native frameworks.
- Partnering with development team members across the globe to create applications that help Associates in their daily work environments.
- Supporting other teams' development projects as needed. I.e. project architecture mapping, specific feature development and application optimization.
- Mentoring junior developers with 1:1 React/React Native teaching sessions and career/ goal planning.

Mobile and Web Application Developer Tabbert Technologies, LLC - Bentonville, AR

Sept 2018 - present

 Partnering with nonprofits and local businesses to create websites and mobile applications using WordPress (JS/PHP), ReactJS, React Native and Native Android.

• Focusing on reaching customers, donors, and recipients using modern UI/UX principles and SEO optimization for maximum reach.

Frontend Developer (Remote)

Jul 2017 - Jun 2018

Chingu - Toronto, Canada

- Front end development of the original Chingu Developer Network client using React and interfacing with a Node/GraphQL/PostgreSQL backend.
- Facilitate 8-10 week long Voyage cohorts of 350 persons across 75 nations.

PROJECTS

<u>Chingu.io</u>: Front end development of the Chingu Development Network client using React and interfacing with a Node/GraphQL/PostgreSQL backend.

 $\underline{\textbf{Designsteins}} \textbf{:} \ \textbf{Design company site using React, routing and map integration}.$

ModMemes: Meme Library web application using MERN stack.

<u>TuVotoTuIdioma</u>: WordPress based informational site for a non-profit, All Voting Is Local, using php, jQuery and HTML5/CSS3.

JuniperMail: Survey generation site using MERN stack with Stripe and Sendgrid.

Bearbnb: Clone of Airbnb using ReactJS/Redux, Express, Node.js and MongoDB.

<u>Vannya-MERN-app</u>: NPM published boilerplate package for creating MERN apps.

Momentum: Clone of productivity Chrome Tab Extension using React/Firebase.

<u>Vannya.me</u>: Portfolio site using React where additional work can be found.

EDUCATION

Associates of Applied Science, Software Development
North Lake College - Irving, TX

Dec 2017

Programming in Java and C++. President's Honor Roll. GPA 3.95

Associates of Arts, Liberal Studies

May 2017

North Lake College - Irving, TX

Areas: Accounting, Calculus, Geology and Photography. GPA 3.92